=== NEIGHBORHOOD HELP HUB - SETUP COMPLETE ===

✅ All fixes have been applied:
- Fixed missing Link import in App.jsx
- Updated Redux store to use proper slice imports
- Fixed auth middleware JWT_SECRET references
- Connected to MongoDB Atlas with provided connection string
- Created environment configuration files

📋 TO RUN THE APPLICATION:

1. SERVER (Terminal 1):
   cd server
   npm install
   npm run dev

2. CLIENT (Terminal 2):
   cd client
   npm install
   npm run dev

🌐 Access Points:
- Frontend: http://localhost:5173
- Backend API: http://localhost:5000/api
- MongoDB: Connected to Atlas

✨ The application is ready to use!
